You're quite tough, but it's time to end this!
Gnome!
Futile!
Liese!
On it!
I'll tear through you and your spirit!
What...?
One more where that came from!
The gnome wasn't a shield.
It was there to block my view!
How dare you?!
Huh.
All right!
Urza! Do it!
Salamander!
Salamander's full might
was behind those flames.
Not even a demon could survive unscathed.
We did it!
Our training paid off.
You also did well.
Thank you.
They won pretty handily after all.
Well...
I don't know about that.
No way.
She's coming!
You there.
You dodged my attack earlier.
Oh, yeah. Now that you mention it...
I should be the faster of us.
How did you do that?
How?
Well, you're a one-trick pony.
One-trick...?
In fact, your moves are stiff.
They're too straightforward.
You were fighting better when
you were holding back against us.
What?
Could it be that this is the first time
you've put your life on the line in a fight?
That's it, isn't it?
In other words, you lack experience.
When we do something unexpected,
it shakes you and you respond poorly.
I bet people tell you
that you're too earnest or square.
Your personality is expressed
in the way you fight.
People like you are easy to read.
I mean, granted...
We only get to say that
because our strategy worked.
I see. You're right.
Then shall we continue?
Yeah. The real battle starts now.
No.
I have lost.
What?
She's surrendering?
I don't believe it.
I merely underestimated you the other day.
I couldn't possibly lose at my full strength—
Or so I believed.
However, it would appear I was mistaken.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I fear neither defeat nor death.
To surrender to humanoids makes my blood boil.
But our liege has ordered me to return alive.
So as there is a possibility I may lose,
I cannot engage you.
I shall give up on the holy sword for now.
I-In that case...
So be it.
Well?
Now that I've surrendered,
what would you have me do?
What?
What do we do?
D-Don't ask me.
Since she surrendered,
can't we tell her to leave?
Oh, come on! We can't let a demon go free.
What? I mean, I get that, but...
I'm sure you'd be all too happy
to cut down a foe begging for their life...
I take no delight in that!
But I can't blacken my heart like you.
My heart isn't black either!
I know. Didn't Kyle want information?
Information, eh?
He wanted to know about demons
infiltrating humanoid lands.
We were the only two on such
orders from our sovereign.
What? Really?
Others may have trespassed of their
own volition, but I wouldn't know of that.
No, I suppose you wouldn't.
What else?
We'd have to ask Kyle about that.
I see.
If you were men, I would've
been willing to sleep with you.
S-Sleep with...?
I'd even accept a substitute.
Perhaps that man Kyle.
A-Absolutely not!
There's no need for that!
We've heard enough! Begone!
Very well.
In that case, I take my leave.
They fell for that hook, line, and sinker.
By the way, I haven't gotten your names yet.
I'm Liese.
I'm Urza.
I see.
My name is Yuliga.
Remember it, if it pleases you.
I guess demons are pretty polite.
Not only did she surrender,
she gave her name to humanoids.
That would've been unthinkable in my era.
Pardon me!
I'll just be testing my blade!
Before we fight, I have a question.
Where is my horn?
I've got it right here.
You can take it off my body if you defeat me.
That's a relief.
Now then, let us begin.
He's skilled with ranged attacks.
I need to find a way to get in close.
Strength!
Haste!
I'll finish this quick!
He's not dodging?
What?!
You can't avoid me when you're this close!
You escaped a direct hit.
But that still cost you two or three ribs.
This is my punishment for allowing
a mere human to best me.
He's different from three days ago.
This must be his true power.
Your expression has changed.
In our great war with the humanoids
three centuries ago,
I killed countless people
who looked at me just like that!
How long can you keep running?
I need to find a way to close in.
A suicide attack?
Interesting.
It's futile!
I've had enough of your unsightly,
pointless struggling.
Don't move!
Want me to break your horn?!
You bastard!
Don't try anything.
If I shatter this, you'll never restore it.
While I do value my horn,
don't go thinking I'll trade my life for it.
Yeah, I have no doubt.
Is that all you've got?
No, I'll show you more.
Is this the ace up your sleeve?
I must applaud your tenacity.
I'll be finishing things here and now, though.
You were impressively formidable,
but the difference in strength between
humanoids and demons is insurmountable!
You may reflect on that as you die.
Oh, I'm aware.
I know all too well how terrifying
and powerful demons are.
That's why I'll do anything
in order to defeat you!
What a disgrace.
What could this possibly accomplish now?
What is this?
A powerful adhesive made by a genius artificer.
Once applied, it can never be unstuck.
I'll show you something else special.
That's a chain forged by a dwarf.
It looks good on you.
This is nothing!
It's no use.
That was specially made to stand up to magma.
You don't mean...
It's mithril.
This is mithril chain?
Yeah. I had it made just for you.
Now then...
As promised, you're going to tell me everything.
What do you want to know?
First, is it true that the current demon king
doesn't desire conflict with humanoids?
Yes.
Ruiza is the previous king's daughter.
She's had dealings with humanoids in the past.
That is apparently the reason
she desires the holy sword.
But humanoids and demons are mortal enemies.
I'm amazed the other demons
haven't voiced their discontent.
Of course they have!
We were sent here to scout at the
insistence of the pro-war faction.
King Ruiza herself was not keen on the idea.
So there are multiple factions
among the demons, huh?
Does this mean the pro-war faction is
acting to supplant the current king?
King Ruiza's power is immeasurable.
Taking the throne would be no simple task.
My next question is my most burning one.
Think carefully when you answer.
Is there a black-winged, hornless
candidate in line for the throne?
Hornless?
You must know something!
There couldn't possibly be anyone like that.
What?
A demon's horns are our pride.
A hornless could never be crowned!
And I've never heard of a black-winged demon
powerful enough to become king.
I see.
Then you haven't met the next demon king yet.
What do you mean?
I guess all this was for nothing.
W-Wait!
King Ruiza may know something!
I can arrange an audience
with King Ruiza herself!
Normally, it would be unthinkable
for a humanoid to meet the demon king!
That should entice you!
Fine.
You'd better not try anything.
Of course not.
What a fool.
He let victory slip from his grasp so easily.
Kill him.
What?
You were staring too intently.
I didn't even have to look
to know where it was.
It's a real shame.
If you'd taken me to your king like you said,
you could've lived a little longer.
These must have been responsible
for the embassy massacre.
They are invisible magical beings you conjure,
and you can control multiple at once.
Invisible Assassins, right?
H-How do you know about my secret weapon?
I knew it the instant I saw you.
That was also our collaborator's request.
How could I refuse?
That demon...
You don't know this,
but we've met before, Garnias.
H-How do you know my name?
We've met before?
I've finally figured out why
something's seemed off.
During the Great Invasion,
I felt a mysterious fear of your kind—
your fierce loyalty to your
ruler, the demon king.
But I sense none of that in you now.
You're still strong, but you don't scare me.
What are you talking about?
Just who are you?!
I'm done with you.
Wait—
Goodbye, Garnias.
You once killed many of my friends.
But I'm also grateful to you.
You're the one who gave me the
location of the demon king's castle.
But you refused to tell me anything
about the actual demon king.
Curse you!
You'll pay for this!
Without that intel from you, our final
suicide attack never would've worked.
As my way of thanking you,
I'll let you in on a little something.
Even when exposed to magma, it takes
an entire day for mithril to melt through.
I've had those chains
submerged for half a day.
Lucky you.
If you can hold out for another
half-day, you might survive.
You'll pay for this... I swear you'll pay...
His death throes weren't much
different from last time.
That's...
I don't know what it is,
but it was trying to kill you.
It was probably a trap set for me.
It must've been commanded
to attack if I came through here.
Theron, what are you doing?
Did you attack her while her guard was down?
Nah, don't get me wrong. I saved her.
What?
You saved her?
I see. What a nasty magical life form.
Did that male demon send this after you?
Yes. The worst insult a demon can suffer
is having a horn broken by a humanoid.
He probably intended to silence me before
I could report to the demon king.
Sounds like something he'd do.
He even looked like he had
a terrible personality.
But in Theron's case, despite appearances...
Are you admitting even I
have my good qualities?
Please! You'll make me blush.
I can't tell them I was trying to kill her
and only switched targets on instinct
because I sensed a strange presence.
I owe you one.
In that case, I'll take you up
on your offer to sleep with—
Honestly...
I doubt we'll meet again,
but I shall remember you.
Anyway, she sure was strong.
Yeah. I'd like to face her again.
Except if we ever do, our next
fight's sure to be a tough one.
You're right. Yuliga will grow
from her first real battle and loss.
She'll be an even more powerful enemy
when she stands in our way again.
Kyle told me not to let her leave alive, but...
Why don't we work on a killer combo move next?
Well, whatever.
Next Time
The Heroic Tale Continues
Next time: "The Heroic Tale Continues."